<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_content">
        <p><span class="c7 c10">CDC Obesity Project - Patient Facing Part</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1"><span>A) Data:</span></p><p class="c1"><span>1. Nutrition Status including daily diet, calorie etc.</span></p><ul class="c6 lst-kix_u9jt8a3kdwtt-0 start"><li class="c1 c8"><span>There are several categraies under daily diet, like fruit, drink, vegetable, which come from Aly.</span></li><li class="c1 c8"><span>Calorie can be calculated by physician team if that is more reasonable.</span></li><li class="c1 c8"><span>Food identify results could be applied into calculating and recommendation </span></li></ul><p class="c1"><span>2. We need patient;s location to build our online community.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>; ; Patients can share how or where they exerice. A server is needed to same this data ; </span></p><p class="c1"><span>; ; including words, pictures and videos.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>; ; Another function is to record patient;s physical activity like many wearable devices, </span></p><p class="c1"><span>; ; including time, distance, activity level.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>3. Patient;s BMI. The history of BMI is better if it is available, which can show the trend so </span></p><p class="c1"><span>; ; that physician and patient can analyze and utilize it.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>4. Account information contains basic EHR which can also be used for diet </span></p><p class="c1"><span>; ; recommendation. However, I am not sure which data we decide to use, so this accout </span></p><p class="c1"><span>; ; may base on FHIR or different information.</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1"><span>B)Functions:</span></p><p class="c1"><span>1)Food Identify</span></p><p class="c1"><span>Users can use ;Food Identify; to record what they eat and calculate nutrition roughly.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>Users can choose take a picture or pick a photo from gallery to identify. Instead of these two, users can also use the frequent tags at the bottom of screen.The results of food identifying are food name tags just like these.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>After identifying, users can select right tags by clicking or type in food names by themselves.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>Then they will be led to the quantity page where they can enter how many of food. The unit here is designed as a cup or one piece which is not so precise but more friendly to users.</span></p><p class="c1"><span>At last, users will record or upload if they want the food data by clicking submit button. Of course, they can press redo to return to tags page.</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1"><span>2)Community</span></p><p class="c1"><span>We design this part following some other mature social apps which we believe are much easy for users to understand. Users can browser all posts in the main page by scrolling up and down. They can make friend with others by clicking their name and asking for it. Also, they can post a new one by clicking post button at the top of screen which leads them to a post page. Furthermore, there is a event button on the right-top which will show users a list with all available events nearby. All events and posts in this part are relevant to health food or physical exercise.</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1"><span>3)Health Status</span></p><p class="c1"><span>Users learn their BMI and nutrition intake status in charts, they can also obtain more information by clicking chart and entering detail page. Users can also type in BMI and nutrition information manually which will be uploaded and verified by their physicians. Since the account is binded to EHR, users can watch their EHR, prescriptions or physicians; advice in this part.</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1"><span>Notes:</span></p><p class="c1"><span>FHIR Enable Epic EHR using Cloverleaf ;HUMC</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1"><span>Patient demographics update (Registration)(Questionnaires)</span></p><p class="c1"><span>Patient Appointment</span></p><p class="c1"><span>Open Scheduling</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p><p class="c0 c11"><span class="c3 c7">Details on Health Status Function</span></p><p class="c0" id="h.4uhyq545e78f"><span class="c3">Function of Health Status primarily contains two sub-functions: CDC BMI Analysis and User Feedback. </span></p><p class="c0 c2" id="h.gjdgxs"><span class="c3"></span></p><ul class="c6 lst-kix_nvzwtxw3e6w2-0 start"><li class="c0 c8 c9"><span class="c3 c7">CDC BMI Analysis</span></li></ul><p class="c0"><span class="c3">Specific data which should be provided in this part includes: Date of Birth, Date of Measurement, Sex, Height (to nearest 1/8 inch), and Weight (to nearest ; pound). </span></p><p class="c0"><span class="c3">For BMI analysis part, BMI calculated for children and teens is particularly emphasized here. In order to calculate BMI for children and teens, parents or guardians are supposed to measure children;s </span><span class="c3 c4">height</span><span class="c3">;and </span><span class="c3 c4">weight</span><span class="c3">;accurately. A guidance that can help parents or guardians to measure them accurately can be provided by this app. </span></p><p class="c0"><span class="c3">A calculator provides BMI for children should be designed. A </span><span class="c3 c4">CDC BMI-for-age Growth Chart</span><span class="c3">;should be used as standard to design this calculator. A BMI calculator offered by CDC specifically for children aged 2 through 19 years old can be considered as a reference. </span></p><p class="c0"><span class="c3">In order to make comparisons, percentiles data should also be provided to app users. These percentiles express a child;s BMI relative to children in the U.S. who participated in national surveys that were conducted from 1963-65 to 1988-944. Because weight and height change during growth and development, as does their relation to body fatness, a child;s BMI must be interpreted relative to other children of the same sex and age.</span></p><p class="c0"><span class="c3">At last, the app should also be designed to alert users that this BMI calculator is not meant to serve as a source of clinical guidance and is not intended to be a substitute for professional medical advice. Because BMI is based on weight and height, it is only an indicator of body fatness. Individuals with the same BMI may have different amounts of body fat. Persons may consider seeking advice from their health-care providers on healthy weight status and to consider individual circumstances.</span></p><p class="c0 c2"><span class="c3"></span></p><ul class="c6 lst-kix_nvzwtxw3e6w2-0"><li class="c0 c8"><span class="c3 c7">User Feedback</span></li></ul><p class="c0 c2"><span class="c3"></span></p><p class="c0"><span class="c3">Reference:</span></p><p class="c0"><span class="c3">&quot;About Child &amp; Teen BMI.&quot; </span><span class="c3 c4">Centers for Disease Control and Prevention</span><span class="c3">. Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, 15 May 2015. Web. 23 Feb. 2016.</span></p><p class="c1 c2"><span></span></p>

    </string>
</resources>