<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="about_content">
        <![CDATA[
        <h1>CDC Obesity Project - Patient Facing Part</h1>
        <h2>A) Data:</h2>
        <p>1. Nutrition Status including daily diet, calorie etc.</p>
        <ul>
            <li>There are several categraies under daily diet, like fruit, drink, vegetable, which come from Aly.</li>
            <li>Calorie can be calculated by physician team if that is more reasonable.</li>
            <li>Food identify results could be applied into calculating and recommendation</li>
        <p>2. We need patient’s location to build our online community.
            Patients can share how or where they exerice. A server is needed to same this data
            including words, pictures and videos.
            Another function is to record patient’s physical activity like many wearable devices,
            including time, distance, activity level.</p>
        <p>3. Patient’s BMI. The history of BMI is better if it is available, which can show the trend so
            that physician and patient can analyze and utilize it.</p>
        <p>4. Account information contains basic EHR which can also be used for diet
            recommendation. However, I am not sure which data we decide to use, so this accout
            may base on FHIR or different information.</p>

        <h2>B)Functions:</h2>
            <h3>1)Food Identify</h3>
            <p>Users can use “Food Identify” to record what they eat and calculate nutrition roughly.
            Users can choose take a picture or pick a photo from gallery to identify. Instead of these two, users can also use the frequent tags at the bottom of screen.The results of food identifying are food name tags just like these.
            <p>After identifying, users can select right tags by clicking or type in food names by themselves.</p>
            Then they will be led to the quantity page where they can enter how many of food. The unit here is designed as a cup or one piece which is not so precise but more friendly to users.
            At last, users will record or upload if they want the food data by clicking submit button. Of course, they can press redo to return to tags page.</p>
        <h3>2)Community</h3>
        <p>We design this part following some other mature social apps which we believe are much easy for users to understand. Users can browser all posts in the main page by scrolling up and down. They can make friend with others by clicking their name and asking for it. Also, they can post a new one by clicking post button at the top of screen which leads them to a post page. Furthermore, there is a event button on the right-top which will show users a list with all available events nearby. All events and posts in this part are relevant to health food or physical exercise.</p>
        <h3>3)Health Status</h3>
        <p>Users learn their BMI and nutrition intake status in charts, they can also obtain more information by clicking chart and entering detail page. Users can also type in BMI and nutrition information manually which will be uploaded and verified by their physicians. Since the account is binded to EHR, users can watch their EHR, prescriptions or physicians’ advice in this part.</p>

        <h2>Notes:</h2>
        <p>FHIR Enable Epic EHR using Cloverleaf  HUMC<p>

        <ul><li>Patient demographics update (Registration)(Questionnaires)</li>
        <li>Patient Appointment</li>
        <li>Open Scheduling</li><ul>
        ]]>
    </string>
</resources>